The drama's starting again, smoke in the kitchen
Drop the keys out to the street, don't you wanna see how it ends?
I'm only 20 but it feels like plenty, man I still get blown but I don't sit Henny
I'm laying in the back of the Maybach Benny, 2025 yeah my jeans still heady
This is paint not blood, I'm feeling pain I'm sipping syrup, smoking up, I feel it in my brain
Try dress like me, we are not the same I'm a winner man, this rap shit is a fucking game
You ain't killing shit bitch, you a fucking lame I got my own hair, a scream in my fucking name
Yeah your bitch an animal, you need a fucking tamer I'm really balling like I'm PSG Neymar
I dance in the rain like Snoop, when it's day time, Bottega You don't know what it feels like, hesitate
I only do it when it feels right, Jelanie You know I really got a smoke right
Skinny bitch, she need E.B.Colt line She want my coat cause she cold in this moonlight
We lock eyes, both know that the mood's right Snow white in a black coat, red light
The drama's starting again Smoke in the kitchen
Drop the keys down to the street Don't you wanna see how it ends?
Left a hole in the roof Nothing to remember you
Only true perfume Won't never be seen here again
Na-na-nodding off the Macca I ain't calling bacca
I'm really smoking flavours And Bottega got my bag up
Walking to the store Ain't even looking at the tagger
I'm really living two lives animal
Na-na-nodding off the Macca I ain't calling bacca
Really smoking flavours And Bottega got my bag up
Walking to the store Ain't even looking at the tagger
I'm really living two lives animal
Tip on my bracelet Sniff me a break
Quit chewing this gum But I still fucking taste it
I know it ain't a race But I'm first fucking place
Bitch I know you ain't the one Yeah I see it in your face bitch
My new money look like old money Cosplaying motherfuckers got no money
People really try by taste And they can't
Man you have it or you don't
Yeah sad but it's so funny I got that wack
Ooh let me feel like Snow Bunny
Yeah that wack, wack, wack Got my nose running
Yeah that wack, wack, wack Got my wack, wack